Thank you for downloading.
Please follow all rules.

DO NOT:
- Redistribute/reupload the motion or camera in any way.
- Convert to different formats. My motions are for MMD only.
- Edit the motion or camera and redistribute it.
- Use for commercial purposes. My motions are for free personal use only.
- Share the download password.
- Use in R-18 videos.
- Claim as your own.

You are allowed, in fact I encourage you, to edit the motion or camera to fit your model or fix any clipping or glitches. Just don't redistribute the edited versions.

When using the motion or camera in any video, ALWAYS credit LadieAlien and/or link back to my original video in your description.

——————————————————————————————————————
YouTube:	http://youtube.com/c/ladiealien
Patreon:	http://patreon.com/ladiealien
Twitter:	http://twitter.com/ladiealien
——————————————————————————————————————