【REM's Hatsune Miku V4X】
-Modeller: REMmaple
-Design：iXima
-Copyright: Crypton Future Media inc., PIAPRO

Thank you for downloading!

【About】
This folder contains:
1 - MMD Model
2 - Textures, sphere maps, toon
3 - Readme

-The data contained in this folder is Hatsune Miku V4X  MMD model based on its official design 
-The usage of these data has some limits, please respect them.

-The official rules of this character is on Piapro character license of Crypton Future Media inc.
http://piapro.jp/license/character_guideline

【Forbidden】
1 - Commercial,political, religious use
2 - R-18，violence
3 - Contempt towards countries or people
4 - Deceiving/Claiming to be the original creator
5 - Used to create illegal productions
6 - violating public and order, lack of wise and subtle judgment.

【Redistribution and edit】 
1 - Allowed to edit and redistribution(the character has to be Hatsune Miku), but all parts of this model CAN'T be transplanted on other models.
( e.g.: The headphones, Outfit, etc )

2 - When redistributing, the Japanese readme.txt and this readme.txt MUST be in the same folder

【Disclaimer】
The creator( REMmaple ) of this model data is not responsible for any damage caused by using this model

【Acknowledgements/Programs used】
Everything is made possible with those programs, thanks to the program creators.

-MikuMikuDance                higuchuu / 樋口優
-PMXEditor                    KyokuhokuP / 極北P
-Metasequoia                  tetraface Inc.
-Photoshop CS6                Adobe 

【Contacts】
-DeviantArt       REMmaple.deviantart.com
-Twitter         @REMmaple 
-Weibo           @REMmaple